Guide to the Victor S. Navasky Papers TAM.594
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Audio-Visual Materials, 1976-1996, undated
  - Subseries XA: Audio Cassettes
    - Naming Names - Unidentified, undated (Box 91, Cassette 19)
    - Naming Names - Australian Parliament, US legislation, Stan Curry (Australian radio program), undated (Box 93, Cd 22, Box 91, Cassette 20)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #1 (Box Shared Tamiment 070)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #2(a) and 2(b) (Box 92)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #2(c) (Box 92)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #3(a) and 3(b) (Box 92)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #3(c) (Box Shared Tamiment 070)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #4(a) and 4(b) (Box 92)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #4(c) (Box 92)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: #5(a) and 5(b) (Box 92)
    - Sessions Recorded at Bellagio Conference: unlabeled tape (Box 92)
    - Various - Communications and Society Seminar - Unfolding Lotus, Oct 21, 1993 (Box 92, Cassette 21)
    - Various - Ehrenreich, Barbara, Mar 15, 1994 (Box 92, Cassette 22)
    - Various - Eisenstein, Elizabeth Fellows Seminar "The End of the Book", Nov 29, 1995 (Box Shared Tamiment 070, Cassette 23)
    - Various - Hertzberg, Hendrik, Feb 22, 1994 (Box 92, Cassette 24)
    - Various - Hetterman, Ray, Mar 1, 1994 (Box 92, Cassette 25)
    - Various - Hitchens, Christopher, undated (Box 92, Cassette 26)
    - Various - Kennedy, Randy, undated (Box 92, Cassette 27)
    - Various - Kuttner, Bob, Mar 8, 1994 (Box 92, Cassette 28)
    - Various - "Navasky", undated (Box 92, Cassette 29)
    - Various - Open Mind, Presenter: Edward Mortimer, Producer: Gwyneth Williams, Aug 6, 1991 (Box 92, Cassette 30)
    - Various - O'Sullivan, Mar 22, 1994 (Box 92, Cassette 31)
    - Various - Rosenberg Debate, Swarthmore College (Tape 1), Apr 13, 1996 (Box 92, Cassette 32)
    - Various - Rosenberg Debate, Swarthmore College (Tape 2), Apr 13, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 070, Cassette 33)
    - Various - Sherman Discussion: Models of Ownership, 1999-12-29 (Box Shared Tamiment 070)
    - Various - Southern California Library for Social Sciences and The Nation Magazine's 125th Year (Tape 1), Feb 3, 1991 (Box 92, Cassette 34)
    - Various - Southern California Library for Social Sciences and The Nation Magazine's 125th Year (Tape 2), Feb 3, 1991 (Box 92, Cassette 35)
    - Various - Stone, I.F.: The Nation Institute and The New School present A Conversation with I.F. Stone at 80 (Tape 1), 1987 (Box 92, Cassette 36)
    - Various - Stone, I.F.: The Nation Institute and The New School present A Conversation with I.F. Stone at 80 (Tape 2), 1987 (Box 92, Cassette 37)
  - Subseries XB: Other Formats
    - Children of the Left, produced by Eric Stange, 1958 (Box 94)
    - Unidentified Reel- "McCarthy", undated (Box 94)
    - Unidentified Reel, undated (Box 94)
    - Unidentified Reel, undated (Box 94)
    - Unidentified Reel, undated (Box 94)
    - Unidentified Reel, undated (Box 94)